apnigari.com 2010-06-24

# Privacy Policy : Pakistan's best destination for buying and selling cars : ApniGari.com

We are committed to honor your rights to privacy. ApniGari.com will never sell or make available individual names, lists of users, or aggregate data to any third party. We will not accept   
customer or end user information that your email provider may have collected.

By publishing our Privacy Statement, we allow you to make informed decision whether to utilize our service offerings.

**Personal Information**  
ApniGari.com does require you to provide necessary personal information, which will be used only for billing and internal administration purposes. As such, we do NOT share any information   
with third parties, including email addresses, and we are committed to keeping all information confidential and secured. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse   
and alteration of the information under our control.

**Linked Sites**  
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by ApniGari.com website.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal   
process served on our website.

 **Security Statement**  
ApniGari.com sets strict security policies and access rights to protect against loss, misuse, and alteration of messages stored on our servers. To learn more, ask us about a detailed security   
statement.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. In addition, if we make any   
material changes in our privacy practices that affect user’s information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change.
